Paul Abelson Papers 5192
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Paul Abelson Papers
1902-1965
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Abelson, Paul
5192
52.5 cubic feet
52.5 linear ft.
Papers (documents), clippings (information artifacts), decisions.
Include decisions, correspondence, clippings and other materials relating to arbitration and mediation in a range of industries.
2295993
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, March 14, 2003
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, February 21, 2017
Biographical / Historical
Paul Abelson, the son of Joseph Mayer and Ruchama (Bromber) Abelson was born in Kovno, Lithuania, September 27, 1878. He immigrated to the United States with his parents in 1892. He received his A.B. from the College of the City of New York in 1899, his secondary diploma from the Teacher's College of Columbia University in 1900, and his Ph.D. from Columbia University in 1906. In 1918, he received his L.L.B. from the New York Law School and was admitted to the New York Bar.
Mr. Abelson's career was most closely connected with the labor movement. In 1910, he entered the field of labor arbitration when he was appointed a member of the conciliation staff under the arbitration plan of the cloak and suit industry of New York City.
Throughout his career, he continued to serve as a labor arbitrator for many other industries including: the paper box industry, the hosiery industry, the fur, millinery, men's hat, Jewish baking, and jewelry trades. After the passage of the National Recovery Act in 1933, Abelson was appointed by President Roosevelt as government representative on seven apparel trade boards.
Abelson was a founder of the National Academy of Arbitrators and while alive was regarded as the Dean of that organization.
Abelson also served as a member of the National Panel of Arbitrators of the American Arbitration Association.
He contributed numerous articles on labor, education, and civics to various magazines. He was editor-in-chief of the English-Yiddish Encyclopedia Dictionary (1915); The Dictionary of Fur Names (1921); and the author of The Seven Liberal Arts (1906), a study in medieval education.
Paul Abelson was married in 1905, to Helen Cohen in New York City. They had three children (Miriam [Mrs. Robert Ness], Ruth [Mrs. Harold Ceder], and Louise) and eight grandchildren. On November 4, 1953, he died in New York City at the age of 75.
Biographical / Historical
UNION ABBREVIATIONS
AFFFHW .- American Federation of Full-Fashioned Hosiery Workers
BCWIU - Bakery and Confectionery Workers International Union of America
CHCMW - Cloth, Hat, Cap and Millinery Workers International Union
DTWU - Doll and Toy Workers Union
IJWU - International Jewelry Workers Union
ILGWU - International Ladies Garment Workers Union
ILHPNW - International Ladies Handbag, Pocketbook and Novelty Workers
PNWA - Playthings and Novelty Workers of America
PWU - Pocketbook Workers Union
UCHC - United Cloth Hat and Capmakers of North America
UHCMW - United Hatters, Cap and Millinery Workers International Union
Scope and Contents
Series I., arbitration/mediaion files, arranged alphabetically by industry and Include decisions, correspondence, agreements, and other related documents.
This series includes documentation relative to Mr. Abelson's arbitration and mediation cases. It is arranged alphabetically by industry then divided into four sections: l) decisions, 2) correspondence, 3) agreements, 4) miscellaneous and clippings. Exceptions to this arrangement are the Bakery and Fur Industry's files which begin with minutes being filed first. Another variation is the Cloak and Suit Industry which includes subject files at the end of its arrangement. These were subject headings assigned by Mr. Abelson. Types of documents included in this series are: correspondence, decisions, agreements, briefs, hearings, minutes, clippings, broadsides, meeting announcements, lists of demands, and penciled notes.
Series II, subject files, includes documents, filed alphabetically by subject, not directly related to his arbitration/mediation files.
This series contains material not directly-related to arbitration/mediation cases. This group is broken down alphabetic ally-by subject and includes correspondence, lectures, minutes, notes, course outlines, reports, schedules, memos, charts, releases, articles, clippings and National Recovery-Administration documentation.
Series III, publications, contains articles and publications. Most of the publications were distributed to other locations in the Center such as AUF, AOF, and Rare Pamphlet Collection. A list of these publications is included with the location explained.
Series IV, includes decisions of other Impartial Chairman arranged alphabetically by the Chairman's name.
This series includes decisions of various Impartial Chairmen in the needle trade industries that were filed throughout the Abelson collection. The decisions are filed alphabetically by the name of the Chairman.
Series V, Includes newspaper clippings, miscellaneous and Yiddish documents and broadsides.
A substantial amount of material was identified as Professor Jesse Carpenters' and was removed and placed under collection #5490. Professor Carpenter utilized this collection while writing his book entitled, "Competition and Collective Bargaining In the Needle Trades, 1910-1967."
A separate group of agreements was removed and placed In the Center's Agreement Collection.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 5437 OH: Paul Abelson Interview Conducted by Jesse Carpenter 5490: Jesse Carpenter Records 5807: Paul Abelson Additional Records 6165 mf: Paul Abelson Files on Microfilm
Arbitration, Industrial -- New York (State) -- New York -- Cases; Arbitration, Industrial -- United States -- Cases; Industrial arbitrators; Apprentices -- Arbitration, Industrial -- United States; Arbitration, Industrial -- Bakers and bakeries -- United States; Arbitration, Industrial -- Children's clothing industry -- United States; Arbitration, Industrial -- Clothing industry -- United States; Arbitration, Industrial -- Fur trade -- United States; Arbitration, Industrial -- Hat trade -- United States; Arbitration, Industrial -- Hosiery industry -- United States; Arbitration, Industrial -- Jewelry trade -- United States; Arbitration, Industrial -- Knit goods industry -- United States; Arbitration, Industrial -- Leather industry -- United States; Arbitration, Industrial -- Luggage industry -- United States; Arbitration, Industrial -- Men's clothing industry -- United States; Arbitration, Industrial -- Moving picture industry -- United States; Arbitration, Industrial -- Toy industry -- United States; Arbitration, Industrial -- Women's clothing industry -- United States; Bargaining unit -- Arbitration, Industrial -- United States; Children's clothing industry -- State supervision -- United States; Cleaning and dyeing industry -- State supervision -- New York (State); Collective labor agreements -- Clothing industry -- United States; Contracting out -- Arbitration, Industrial -- United States; Employees, Dismissal of -- Arbitration, Industrial -- United States; Employees, Training of -- Arbitration, Industrial -- United States; Fur trade -- United States -- State supervision; Hat trade -- United States -- State supervision; Hours of labor -- Arbitration, Industrial -- United States; Layoffs -- Arbitration, Industrial -- United States; Lumber industry -- United States -- State supervision; Men's clothing industry -- State supervision -- United States; Piece work -- Arbitration, Industrial -- United States; Position classification -- Arbitration, Industrial -- United States; Strikes and lockouts -- Arbitration, Industrial -- United States; Underwear industry -- United States -- State supervision; Wages -- Arbitration, Industrial -- United States; Wages -- Cleaning and dyeing industry -- New York (State) -- State supervision; Wages -- Clothing industry -- United States; Women's clothing industry -- United States -- State supervision; Work assignments -- Arbitration, Industrial -- United States; Employee rules -- United States; Working conditions -- Arbitration, Industrial -- United States; Allied Association of Clothing Manufacturers; Amalgamated Ladies' Garment Cutters' Union; American Federation of Full-Fashioned Hosiery Workers; American Federation of Labor; Associated Doll Manufacturers of New York, Inc.; Associated Fur Manufacturers; Association of Dress Makers; Atlantic and Gulf Ship Operators Association; Bakery and Confectionery Workers' International Union of America; Bakery Wagon Drivers' Union; Children's Dress and House Dress Workers' Union; Children's Dress Contractors' Association, Inc.; Children's Dress, Cotton Dress and Sportswear Contractors' Association, Inc.; Children's Dress, Infants' Wear, House-dress and Bathrobe Makers' Union; Children's Dress Manufacturers' Association; Children's Dressmakers' Union; Cloak, Suit and Skirt Manufacturers' Protective Association (New York, N.Y.); Cloth Hat, Cap, and Millinery Workers' International Union; Committee on Immediate Action; Cotton Apparel and Robe Producers' Association, Inc.; Dress and Waist Manufacturers' Association of New York; Eastern Women's Headwear Association, Inc.; Embroidery Workers' Union; Full-Fashioned Hosiery Manufacturers of America; Fur Trimming Manufacturers' Association; Furriers' Union of the United States of America and Canada; Guild of Designers, Inc.; Hat Frame Manufacturers' Protective Association, Inc.; Industrial Association of Juvenile Apparel Manufacturers, Inc.; Infants' and Children's Coat Association, Inc.; International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen, and Helpers of America; International Fur and Leather Workers Union of the United States and Canada; International Jewelry Workers Union; International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union; International Ladies' Handbag, Pocketbook and Novelty Workers' Union; International Union of Doll and Toy Workers; International Union of United Brewery, Flour, Cereal, Soft Drink, and Distillery Workers of America; International Union, Playthings and Novelty Workers of America; J.L. Magnes Manufacturers, Inc.; Jewish Community of New York City; John B. Stetson Hat Company; Joint Board of Cloak, Suit, Skirt and Reefer Makers' Union; Joint Board of Fur Cap and Trimming Makers' Union; Joint Board of Furriers' Union of Greater New York and Vicinity; Joint Council of Jewish Bakers; Ladies' Handbag Pocketbook Workers of New York; Ladies' Waist and Dressmakers Union; Leather Goods Manufacturing, Inc.; Metropolitan Bakery and Lunchroom Association; Millinery and Ladies' Straw Hat Workers' Union; Moving Picture Machine Operators Union; Muff Bed Manufacturers' Association, Inc.; National Child Labor Committee (U.S.); National Coat and Suit Industry Recovery Board (U.S.); New York Hotel Trades Council; New York (State). Cloak and Suit Control Commission; New York State Labor Relations Board; Pocketbook Workers' Union of New York; Radio Officers' Union; Specialty Bakery Owners of America, Inc.; Stuffed Toy Manufacturers' Association; Toy and Novelty Workers of America; United Brotherhood of Cloak Makers of New York; United Cloak, Suit and Skirt Manufacturers' Association; United Cloth Hat and Cap Makers of North America; United Hatters, Cap, and Millinery Workers International Union; United Infants' and Children's Wear Association; United States. National Recovery Administration; United Wholesale and Warehouse Employees of New York; Wholesale Dress Manufacturers' Association; Wholesale Hat and Cap Manufacturers' Association; International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union. Local 41 (New York, N.Y.); Abelson, Paul.; Alger, George W. (George William), 1872-1967.; Barnes, Charles B.; Baroff, Abraham; Douglas, Paul H.; Dyche, John A. (John Alexander), 1867-1938; Eckstein, S. W.; Engel, Adolph, 1893-1974; Feldblum, Adolph; Gold, Ben; Greenberg, J. George; Helfer, Joseph E.; Iffland, Charles; Ingersoll, Raymond V. (Raymond Vail), 1875-1940; Kaufman, Morris; Klein, Julius, 1886-; Lehman, Herbert H. (Herbert Henry), 1878-1963; London, Meyer, 1871-1926; Mack, Julian W. (Julian William), 1866-1943; Magnes, Judah Leon, 1877-1948; Mannheimer, Leo, 1878-1954; Marks, Marcus M., 1858- 1934; Mayer, Henry; Merritt, Walter Gordon, 1880-1968; Mills, David C.; Moskowitz, B. L.; Moskowkitz, Henry; Norton, Thomas L. (Thomas Lowell), 1900-1976; Pechter, William; Pike, William; Polakoff, S.; Rogers, Lindsay, 1891-; Rosenblatt, Sol A. (Sol Ariah), 1900-1968; Rosenfeld, L. E.; Samuels, Samuel N.; Schiff, Jacob H. (Jacob Henry), 1847-1920; Schlossberg, Joseph, 1875-1971; Silberman, Morris; Spector, Nathaniel, 1891-; Taylor, George William, 1901-; Walker, James J. (James John), 1881-1946; Willits, Joseph Henry, 1889-; Woll, Matthew, 1880-1956; Zaritsky, Max, 1885-1959
2295993
- Minutes, 1938-1952 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  Scope and Contents
  incomplete, includes index
- Minutes, 1938-1952 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Minutes, 1938-1952 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Minutes, 1938-1952 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Minutes, 1938-1952 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Minutes, 1938-1952 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Minutes, 1938-1952 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Minutes, 1938-1952 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Minutes, 1938-1952 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Minutes, 1938-1952 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Minutes, 1938-1952 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Minutes, 1938-1952 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Minutes, 1932-1941 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  Yiddish
- Minutes, 1932-1941 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Minutes, 1932-1941 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Minutes, 1932-1941 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Minutes, 1932-1941 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Financial Statement and Report, 1933-1948 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Pechter Baking Company and Local 507, Bakery and Confectionery Workers International Union of America (BCWIU), 1931 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  July 23rd
- Speciality Bakery Owners of America, Inc. vs. BCWIU, Jt. Council, and Abraham Walds Treicher and Nathan Korman vs. BCWIU, 1934 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  May 4th-17th
- Isaac Fenster vs. Morris Jainsky, 1935 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  Dec 21st
- Highway Bakery vs. Local 79, BCWIU, 1940 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  Nov 8th
- Barney Newburg vs. Morris Bleyer and Himey Brecker, co-partners, 1941 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  April 25th
- Bloom's Bake Shop vs. Jack Zucker and Speciality Bakery Owners of America, Inc. vs. Locals 1111 and 150, BCWIU, 1946-1948 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  Oct. 7th
- Speciality Bakery Industries, City of I.I, vs. Fass Inc., 1933 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  Nov. 8th
- Brothers vs. BCWIU, Schlesinger vs. BGWIU, Kasimirsky and Rosenblum vs. BCWIU, 1933 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  Nov 8th-17th
- David Dubner vs. Local 505, BCWIU, 1933 (Box 3, Folder 7)
- Speciality Bakery Industries, City of N.Y. vs. Goldstein, 1933 (Box 3, Folder 7)
- Speciality Bakery Owners of America, Inc. vs. Locals 505, 507, 509 and 79, BCWIU, 1933 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  December
- Speciality Bakery Owners Of America, Inc. vs. Locals 505, 507, 509 and 79, BCWIU, 1934 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  Jan. 24th
- Miller Brothers vs. Jt. Council of Jewish Union of Greater NY, 1934 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  June 20th
- Charles Beberman vs. BCWIU, Goldman Bakers vs. BCWIU, Dubner vs. Local 505, BCWIU, 1934 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  August-December
- Zweighaft vs. BCWIU, 1935 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  July 11th
- Spielman vs. local 505, BCWIU, 1935 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  Oct. 9th
- Licht vs. Local 505, BCWIU, 1935 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  Nov. 15th
- Levanda vs. Local 507, BCWIU, 1935 (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Iskowitz vs. Local 505, BCWIU, 1935 (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Spielman vs. Local 505, BCWIU, 1935 (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Speciality Bakery Owners of America, Inc. vs. Iskowitz, 1935 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  June 26th
- Liker vs. Stoller Baking Co., Freider and Dubner vs. BCWIU, 1935 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  January-February
- Sommer vs. Local 505, BCWIU, 1935 (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Public Baiting Co. vs. BCWIU, 1938 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  June 16th
- Ziggeeser vs. Local 507, BCWIU, 1938 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  July 2nd
- Speciality Bakery Owners of America, Inc. vs. United Retail Bakery Employees Union Local 150 of United Retail and Wholesale Employees, 1940 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  January 27th
- Speciality Bakery Owners of America, Inc. vs. United Retail Bakery Employees, 1942 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  January 14th
- Field's Baking Corp. vs. BCIWU, 1943 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  May 12th
- Speciality Bakery Owners of America, Inc. vs. Locals 55, 579, 164 BCIWU, 1948 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  June 21st
- Speciality Bakery Owners of American, Inc. vs. Local 1111 Retail Bakery and Confectionery Employees Union, 1918 (Box 3, Folder 14)
- Speciality Bakery Owners vs. John Bakery, 1949 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  April 19th
- Michael Shapiro vs. H.J. Deutschman, 1949 (Box 3, Folder 15)
- Speciality Bakery Owners of America, Inc. vs. Locals 51, 164, 579, BCIWU, 1951 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  January 2nd
- Toby Julie vs. Local 164, BCWIU, 1951 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  May 28th
- J. Berkowitz vs. Local 51, BCWIU, 1952 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  June 25th
- H. Taubman vs. Local 51, BCIWU, 1952 (Box 3, Folder 17)
- J. Berkowitz vs. Local 51, BGWIU, 1952 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  Oct. 15th
- Correspondence, 1912-1913 (Box 3, Folder 18)
- Correspondence, 1914-1915 (Box 3, Folder 19)
- Correspondence, 1916-1917 (Box 3, Folder 20)
- Correspondence, 1928 (Box 3, Folder 21)
- Correspondence, 1929 (Box 3, Folder 22)
- Correspondence, 1931 (Box 3, Folder 23)
- Correspondence, 1932 (Box 3, Folder 24)
- Correspondence, 1933 (Box 3, Folder 25)
- Correspondence, 1934 (Box 3, Folder 26)
- Correspondence, 1935 (Box 3, Folder 27)
- Correspondence, 1936 (Box 3, Folder 28)
- Correspondence, 1937 (Box 3, Folder 29)
- Correspondence, 1938 (Box 3, Folder 30)
- Correspondence, 1939-1953 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  and undated
- Correspondence, 1939-1953 (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Correspondence, 1939-1953 (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Correspondence, 1939-1953 (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Correspondence, 1939-1953 (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Correspondence, 1939-1953 (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Correspondence, 1939-1953 (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Correspondence, 1939-1953 (Box 4, Folder 8)
- Correspondence, 1939-1953 (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Correspondence, 1939-1953 (Box 4, Folder 10)
- Correspondence, 1939-1953 (Box 4, Folder 11)
- Correspondence, 1939-1953 (Box 4, Folder 12)
- Correspondence, 1939-1953 (Box 4, Folder 13)
- Correspondence, 1939-1953 (Box 4, Folder 14)
- Correspondence, 1939-1953 (Box 4, Folder 15)
- Agreements, 1928-1953 (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Agreements, 1928-1953 (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Agreements, 1928-1953 (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Agreements, 1928-1953 (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Agreements, 1928-1953 (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Agreements, 1928-1953 (Box 5, Folder 6)
- Agreements, 1928-1953 (Box 5, Folder 7)
- Agreements, 1928-1953 (Box 5, Folder 8)
- Agreements, 1928-1953 (Box 5, Folder 9)
- Agreements, 1928-1953 (Box 5, Folder 10)
- Agreements, 1928-1953 (Box 5, Folder 11)
- Agreements, 1928-1953 (Box 5, Folder 12)
- Agreements, 1928-1953 (Box 5, Folder 13)
- Agreements, 1928-1953 (Box 5, Folder 14)
- Agreements, 1928-1953 (Box 5, Folder 15)
- Agreements, 1928-1953 (Box 5, Folder 16)
- Agreements, 1928-1953 (Box 5, Folder 17)
- Agreements, 1928-1953 (Box 5, Folder 18)
- Agreements, 1928-1953 (Box 5, Folder 19)
- Agreements, 1928-1953 (Box 5, Folder 20)
- Agreements, 1928-1953 (Box 5, Folder 21)
- Agreements, 1928-1953 (Box 5, Folder 22)
- Agreements (Box 5, Folder 23)
  Undated
- Clippings (Box 6, Folder 1)
- Clippings (Box 6, Folder 2)
- Clippings (Box 6, Folder 3)
- Clippings (Box 6, Folder 4)
- Clippings (Box 6, Folder 5)
- Clippings (Box 6, Folder 6)
- Clippings (Box 6, Folder 7)
- Clippings (Box 6, Folder 8)
- Clippings (Box 6, Folder 9)
- Clippings (Box 6, Folder 10)
- Clippings (Box 6, Folder 11)
- Clippings (Box 6, Folder 12)
- Clippings (Box 6, Folder 13)
- Clippings (Box 6, Folder 14)
- Clippings (Box 6, Folder 15)
- Clippings (Box 6, Folder 16)
- Clippings (Box 6, Folder 17)
- Clippings (Box 6, Folder 18)
- Clippings (Box 6, Folder 19)
- Clippings (Box 6, Folder 20)
- Clippings (Box 6, Folder 21)
- Clippings (Box 6, Folder 22)
- Clippings (Box 6, Folder 23)
- Clippings (Box 6, Folder 24)
- Clippings (Box 6, Folder 25)
- Undated clippings (Box 6, Folder 26)
- Broadsides, meeting notices, misc. (Box 6, Folder 27)
- Decisions, Agreements, Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1935-1940 (Box 7, Folder 1)
- Top-Flite Sportswear vs. Children's Dress, Cotton Dress and Sportswear Contractors Assn., 1937 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  July 26th
- Joseph Love, Inc. vs. ILGWU, Local 91, 1938 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  April
- Industrial Association of Juvenile Apparel Manufacturers vs. ILGWU, Local 91, 1938 (Box 7, Folder 2)
- S.L. Hoffman and Co. vs. International Ladies Garment Workers Union (ILGWU), Local 91, 1935-1937 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  April to May
- Industrial Association of Juvenile Apparel Manufacturers vs. ILGWU Local 91, 1939 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  June 28th
- United Infants and Children's Wear Association vs. ILGWU, Local 10, 1936 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  January 31st
- Gort Girls Frocks, Inc. vs. ILGWU, Local 91, 1939 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  Nov. 3rd
- Cotton Apparel and Robe Producers Association vs. ILGWU, Local 91, 1940 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  Sept. 17th
- Robert L. Schwartz and Brothers vs. ILGWU, Local 91, 1939 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  Oct. 4th
- Chickie Manufacturing Co. vs. ILGWU, Local 91 (Box 7, Folder 3)
- Gay Children's Dress Co. vs. ILGWU, Local 91, 1939 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  July 27th
- Goldman and Littman vs. ILGWU, Local 91, 1939 (Box 7, Folder 3)
- Industrial Association of Juvenile Apparel Manufacturers vs. ILGWU, Local 91, 1939 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  July 19th
- Little Lady Girl Dress Co. vs. ILGWU, Local 10, 1939 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  June 30th
- Local 91, 1939 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  May 16th
- Robert L. Schwartz and Brothers vs. ILGWU (Box 7, Folder 3)
- Children's Dress Contractors. Association vs. ILGWU, Local 91, 1939 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  April 26th
- Morris Rothman vs. ILGWU, Local 91, 1939 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  April 8th
- Industrial Association of Juvenile Apparel vs. ILGWU, Local 91, 1938 (Box 7, Folder 3)
- B. Galison vs. Children's Dress, Cotton Dress and Sportswear Contractors, 1938 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  April 7th
- Industrial Association of Juvenile Apparel Manufacturers vs. ILGWU, Local 10, 1937 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  December 27th
- Industrial Association of Juvenile Apparel vs. ILGWU, Local 10, 1937 (Box 7, Folder 3)
- Infant's and Children's Novelty Association vs. ILGWU, Local 91, 1937 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  April 13th
- Reinsdorf and Co. vs. ILGWU, Local 91, 1939 (Box 7, Folder 3)
- Max Horowitz vs. ILGWU, Local 91, 1937 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  August 12th
- Children's Dress Industry Correspondence, 1914-1922 (Box 7, Folder 4)
- Children's Dress Industry Correspondence, 1934-1940 (Box 7, Folder 5)
- Children's Dress Industry Agreements, 1914-1939 (Box 7, Folder 6)
- Children's Dress Industry Agreements, 1914-1939 (Box 7, Folder 7)
- Rosenfeld and Weingarten vs. United Cloak, Suit and Skirt Manufacturers Association, ILGWU, 1915 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  Feb. 13th
- Cloaks Suits Protocol Decisions, Committee on Immediate Action, 1914-1915 (Box 8, Folder 1)
- Phil Katz Co. vs. ILGWU, 1918 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  December 21st
- Cloaks and Suits Correspondence, 1910-1911 (Box 8, Folder 3)
- Cloaks and Suits Correspondence, 1912 (Box 8, Folder 4)
- Cloaks and Suits Correspondence, 1913 (Box 8, Folder 5)
- Cloaks and Suits Correspondence, 1913 (Box 8, Folder 6)
- Cloaks and Suits Correspondence, 1913 (Box 8, Folder 7)
- Cloaks and Suits Correspondence, 1915-1918 (Box 8, Folder 8)
- Cloaks and Suits Correspondence, 1919-1949 (Box 8, Folder 9)
- Undated miscellaneous (Box 8, Folder 10)